export const questions = [{'question': 'Which of the following is the responsibility of a Scrum Master?', 'options': ['Assigning tasks to developers during the Sprint.', 'Ensuring the Scrum Team follows Scrum theory, practices, and rules.', 'Writing user stories and prioritizing the Product Backlog.', 'Approving the final product increment before it is delivered.'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'The Scrum Master ensures that the Scrum Team follows Scrum principles, helps remove impediments, and coaches the team to adopt Agile values.'}, {'question': 'When does a Sprint officially end?', 'options': ['When the timebox expires.', 'When all Product Backlog items are completed.', 'When the Product Owner decides to end it.', 'When the Scrum Master determines the team has delivered enough value.'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'A Sprint officially ends when the timebox expires, regardless of whether all tasks are completed. The team adapts unfinished work in future sprints.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 3?', 'options': ['Option A3', 'Option B3', 'Option C3', 'Option D3'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 3.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 4?', 'options': ['Option A4', 'Option B4', 'Option C4', 'Option D4'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 4.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 5?', 'options': ['Option A5', 'Option B5', 'Option C5', 'Option D5'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 5.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 6?', 'options': ['Option A6', 'Option B6', 'Option C6', 'Option D6'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 6.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 7?', 'options': ['Option A7', 'Option B7', 'Option C7', 'Option D7'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 7.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 8?', 'options': ['Option A8', 'Option B8', 'Option C8', 'Option D8'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 8.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 9?', 'options': ['Option A9', 'Option B9', 'Option C9', 'Option D9'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 9.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 10?', 'options': ['Option A10', 'Option B10', 'Option C10', 'Option D10'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 10.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 11?', 'options': ['Option A11', 'Option B11', 'Option C11', 'Option D11'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 11.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 12?', 'options': ['Option A12', 'Option B12', 'Option C12', 'Option D12'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 12.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 13?', 'options': ['Option A13', 'Option B13', 'Option C13', 'Option D13'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 13.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 14?', 'options': ['Option A14', 'Option B14', 'Option C14', 'Option D14'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 14.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 15?', 'options': ['Option A15', 'Option B15', 'Option C15', 'Option D15'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 15.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 16?', 'options': ['Option A16', 'Option B16', 'Option C16', 'Option D16'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 16.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 17?', 'options': ['Option A17', 'Option B17', 'Option C17', 'Option D17'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 17.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 18?', 'options': ['Option A18', 'Option B18', 'Option C18', 'Option D18'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 18.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 19?', 'options': ['Option A19', 'Option B19', 'Option C19', 'Option D19'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 19.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 20?', 'options': ['Option A20', 'Option B20', 'Option C20', 'Option D20'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 20.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 21?', 'options': ['Option A21', 'Option B21', 'Option C21', 'Option D21'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 21.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 22?', 'options': ['Option A22', 'Option B22', 'Option C22', 'Option D22'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 22.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 23?', 'options': ['Option A23', 'Option B23', 'Option C23', 'Option D23'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 23.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 24?', 'options': ['Option A24', 'Option B24', 'Option C24', 'Option D24'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 24.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 25?', 'options': ['Option A25', 'Option B25', 'Option C25', 'Option D25'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 25.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 26?', 'options': ['Option A26', 'Option B26', 'Option C26', 'Option D26'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 26.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 27?', 'options': ['Option A27', 'Option B27', 'Option C27', 'Option D27'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 27.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 28?', 'options': ['Option A28', 'Option B28', 'Option C28', 'Option D28'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 28.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 29?', 'options': ['Option A29', 'Option B29', 'Option C29', 'Option D29'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 29.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 30?', 'options': ['Option A30', 'Option B30', 'Option C30', 'Option D30'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 30.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 31?', 'options': ['Option A31', 'Option B31', 'Option C31', 'Option D31'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 31.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 32?', 'options': ['Option A32', 'Option B32', 'Option C32', 'Option D32'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 32.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 33?', 'options': ['Option A33', 'Option B33', 'Option C33', 'Option D33'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 33.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 34?', 'options': ['Option A34', 'Option B34', 'Option C34', 'Option D34'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 34.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 35?', 'options': ['Option A35', 'Option B35', 'Option C35', 'Option D35'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 35.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 36?', 'options': ['Option A36', 'Option B36', 'Option C36', 'Option D36'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 36.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 37?', 'options': ['Option A37', 'Option B37', 'Option C37', 'Option D37'], 'correct': 1, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 37.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 38?', 'options': ['Option A38', 'Option B38', 'Option C38', 'Option D38'], 'correct': 2, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 38.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 39?', 'options': ['Option A39', 'Option B39', 'Option C39', 'Option D39'], 'correct': 3, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 39.'}, {'question': 'Sample Scrum question number 40?', 'options': ['Option A40', 'Option B40', 'Option C40', 'Option D40'], 'correct': 0, 'explanation': 'This is an explanation for question 40.'}];